

CARLOS VARGAS

Interdisciplinary Artist 646-972-9433

Vargc12@gmail.com Bronx NY

SKILLS

I am able to learn new skills at a fast pace, I can work well with others in a multiperson enviornment and can contribute ideas for productivy.

I am well versed in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, and Premier Pro.

I Understand the basics of Block Printing, screen printing, and linoleum block pirnts.

Bilingual in spanish and english.

PROFILE

Ive used Adobe programs for 5 years, I am very famialiar with the current updates for Illustrator and Photoshop, I know the basics of video editing and sound editing on Premier Pro and Adobe Audition. I work well with others and have been commended on my ability to pick up skills and adapt to a fast paced work enviornment if needed. I have great communication skills and respond quickly.

EDUCATION

2023

Parsons School of Design Bachelors of Fine Arts

CERTFICATIONS

Certified in Adobe Illustrator.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Studio Assistant

2018-2021

Studio Assistant to abstract painter in the South Bronx. Assisted with production of artwork, goods, and maintenance of studio.

ArtsConnection

Office Assistant 2019-2020

Organized excel sheets with students name, contact information and art piece data. Clerical work.

Parsons Scholar Program / Mentor 2019- 2023

Mentor for Highschool sophmores, juniors, and seniors. Assisted in the planning of activities ranging from trip planning to guest artist vistits.

ArtsConnection

Freelance 2020-Current

Photographer, gallery instalation and planning, art handeling, and art packaging.

Artist Assistant

2023

Studio assistant to a soft structure artist.

Bronx Museum

2018

Edited and conducted artist interviews using camcorders and editing with Premier Pro and Imovie.